Bună, ați sunat la Linia
Telefonică Madonna.
Hi, this is Telephone
Communication Madonna.
Să vedem. Numărul
tău de membru este...
Let's see. Your membership number is...
Oh, ești elev la gimnaziu?
Oh, you're a junior high school student?
Bună, ați sunat la Linia
Telefonică Madonna.
Cum ești în această
seară minunată?
Hi, this is Telephone
Communication Madonna.
How are you doing today?
Nu-ți face griji.
Don't worry.
I poured blue moonlight in a glass
and put it to my lips
It'll ease the pain in your heart
Everyone longs for a stimulus
Let's invite passion to the sky
Sweet music, that's it
Two people in motion in the sky
Please call me tonight, don't forget
Please call me tonight, once again
Alo, Natsumi la telefon.
Ah, Emi. Cum merge cu clubul?
Hi, it's Natsumi. Oh, Emi.
So how's the club going? Well?
Așa și așa.
Nu sunt probleme.
Yeah, not much trouble.
Ce ai zice dacă ai mai trece pe aici
din când în când? Doar tu ești șefa.
Why don't you show your face here
from time to time? You are the boss.
Hei, eu sunt doar proprietara Cooperativei Natsumi,
în ceea ce privește clubul.
Hey, I'm only Natsumi Co-op's owner,
as far as the club goes.
Știu.
I know.
Apropo, Rumi,
By the way, Rumi,
avem un client care are nevoie de tine.
there's a client who needs you.
Poți să notezi numărul?
Can you write down the number?
Dă-i drumul.
Go ahead.
Domnul Sugiura din Mitaka. Problema lui este...
Sugiura-san from Mitaka. His issue is...
O problemă cu masturbarea?!
A masturbation problem?!
Hei, Yumi, ce-i asta?!
Hey, Yumi, what's with this?!
Noi nu ne ocupăm de așa ceva.
We can't handle this.
Ei bine, spune că i se schimbă corpul când se masturbează.
Well, he says his body changes when he masturbates.
Aici Sugiura.
Sugiura here.
Sunt Suuko de la Madonna.
This is Suuko from Madonna.
Ah, s-salut.
Oh, h-hi.
Îți mulțumesc că ai sunat mai devreme.
Thank you for calling earlier.
Ah, păi...
Oh, well...
Vocea ta pare lipsită de viață.
E ceva grav, nu?
Your voice seems dead.
This is serious, huh?
Da, păi...
Yeah, well...
Când mă masturbez,
văd lumini și păsări și alte chestii,
When I masturbate,
I see light and birds and stuff,
iar camera mea este făcută praf.
and my room gets trashed.
H-Hai, calmează-te.
Calmează-te și vorbește cu mine!
H-Hey, just calm down.
Calm down and talk to me!
P-Păi, aș vrea să ne întâlnim
undeva. Ăă...
W-Well, I'd like to meet
somewhere. Um...
Pub Juncha
Rhan
Tegoth
Bine ai venit!
Welcome!
Mulțumesc că ai așteptat!
Thanks for waiting!
O scrumieră pe o carte.
Ashtray on a book.
Acela era semnul.
That was the sign.
Eu sunt Sugiura.
I'm Sugiura.
Eu sunt Suuko. Îmi pare bine să te cunosc!
I'm Suuko. Nice to meet you!
Bine ați venit! Ce doriți?
Welcome! What would you like?
Un Earl Grey cu gheață, vă rog.
Iced Earl Grey, please.
Desigur.
Certainly.
Probabil ai mare succes la fete!
You must be popular with girls!
În legătură cu ce vorbeam mai devreme...
Regarding what we were talking about before...
Nu este chiar o problemă atât de gravă.
It's not such a serious problem.
Am un prieten de vârsta ta care îl cunoaște foarte bine pe Freud.
I have a friend who's about your age and very familiar with Freud.
Potrivit lui, libidoul este...
According to him, the libido is...
Ce na-
Wha-
Ce s-a întâmplat cu hainele tale?!
What happened to your clothes?!
Ori de câte ori încerc... ăă, se întâmplă asta.
Whenever I try... um, this happens.
Poftiți. Poftă bună.
Here you are. Please enjoy.
Presupun că acesta nu este locul potrivit pentru Freud.
I guess this is no place for Freud.
Oricum, nu mai e distractiv dacă e prea ușor.
It's not fun if it's too easy, anyway.
Și trebuie să cheltuiesc o grămadă de bani pe haine.
I have to spend so much on clothes, too.
De ce nu te masturbezi aici?
Why don't you masturbate here?
Nu?
No?
Poate apărea o șopârlă.
Sau chiar un vârcolac.
A lizard might appear.
Maybe even a werewolf.
The Secret of the
Werewolf Village
Hei...
Hey...
Este în regulă.
It's fine.
Întoarce-te încoace.
Face this way.
S-Stai, a-aia e...
W-Wait, th-that's...
Hei, chemați pe cineva o ambulanță.
Hey, someone call an ambulance.
Nu este rănit?
He's not hurt?
H-Hey, ești bine?!
H-Hey, are you all right?!
E-Eu...
I-I...
H-Hai odată!
C-Come on!
Book: The Man with a Thousand Legs
by F. B. Long
Teito Rapid Transit
Scuze!
Sorry!
A-Acum înțeleg la ce te refereai
cu hainele.
I-I can see what you mean
about the clothes.
Tu ai făcut asta?
Was that you?
Ce naiba ești?!
What the hell are you?!
Taci!
Be quiet!
Scuze.
Sorry.
De ce eu?
Why me?
Ce vrei să fac?
What do you want me to do?
Nu am putut să spun nimănui.
Voiam doar să vorbesc despre asta.
I wasn't able to tell anyone.
I just wanted to talk about it.
Așa că...
So...
Așază-te!
Sit down!
Îți spun să te așezi!
I'm tellin' ya to sit down!
Practic, când se gândește la lucruri obscene sau le vede...
So basically, when he thinks or sees lewd things...
Ah, înțeleg.
Oh, I see.
Se simte extraordinar.
De ce nu iei și tu una?
It feels great.
Why don't you take one too?
N-Nu e o idee bună
să vin într-un loc ca acesta.
I-It's a bad idea,
coming to a place like this.
Cu corpul meu în starea asta...
With my body this way...
Prostuțule. Crezi că o să mă culc cu un monstru?
Dummy. You think I'm going to sleep with a monster?
Așa este, dar...
That's true, but...
Dar...
But...
Sunt foarte... interesată de tine.
I'm very... interested in you.
Se pare că am ajuns la ultima soluție.
Looks like we're at the last resort.
Va trebui doar să te obișnuiești.
You'll just have to get used to it.
„S-Să mă obișnuiesc”?!
Teito Rapid Transit
Pub Juncha
"G-Get used to it"?!
Da, să te obișnuiești!
Pub Juncha
Yes, get used to it!
I won't turn off the candle light tonight
Dancing Queen, pretending to be Madonna
Hai, hai, vino!
Now, now, come on!
Queen M
I'll decide what kind of rouge to wear
Private Video
I'm in love, I like my freedom
Pub Juncha
Why is this Friday night so wonderful?
There's a moment of tenderness
when I look at you
I want to hold you right now
Hei!
Yo!
Ce mai faci?
What's up?
SHAGGAI
Și apoi tentaculele astea au făcut bum!
And then these tentacles were like boom!
E adevărat! Nici măcar nu era un costum!
It's true! It wasn't a costume either!
Nu e interesant?
Isn't it interesting?
Un extraterestru, un proiect secret al vreunei țări, o persoană creată artificial!
An alien, some country's secret project, an engineered person!
Nu, o ființă încă nedescoperită...
No, an undiscovered...
Dar este un tip destul de arătos,
nu crezi?
But he's a pretty good-looking guy,
don't you think?
Ca să ajungi să te îndrăgostești de el.
For you to have a crush on him.
Hei, ascultă ce spun!
Hey, listen to what I'm saying!
Nu-ți face idei ciudate, surioară.
E un monstru!
Don't get weird ideas, sister.
He's a monster!
Știu. Este un monstru.
I know. He's a monster.
Tu ești și mai mult
un monstru, totuși.
You're even more
of a monster, though.
Dar... fata asta...
But... this girl...
Unde am mai văzut-o?
Where have I seen her?
Eleva din primul an, Natsumi!
The first year student, Natsumi!
Natsumi Rumi!
Am găsit ceva interesant pentru prima dată după mult timp.
I've found something interesting for the first time in a while.
Fac aceste fotografii.
I'm taking these photos.
Oh, mamă, mă duc la Yumi.
Oh, Mother, I'm going to Yumi's place.
Nu-ți face griji.
Don't worry.
Bine. Pa, mamă.
Okay. Bye, Mother.
Chiar te descurci bine, Natsumi.
That sure is smooth, Natsumi.
Deci eleva-model, Natsumi Rumi,
So the top student, Natsumi Rumi,
se transformă într-o femeie
a nopții, nu?
transforms into a woman
of the night, huh?
C-Ce vrei de la mine?
Wh-What do you want with me?
Nimic.
Nothing.
Vreau doar să-l cunosc
ceva mai bine.
I just want to get a little better acquainted with him.
Este simplu.
It's simple.
Adu-l mâine la ora 4 la barul Shaggai,
de lângă gară.
Bring him to the Shaggai Bar
by the station tomorrow at 4.
Petrece noaptea gândindu-te la ce se va întâmpla dacă refuzi.
Spend the night thinking about what will happen if you refuse.
C-Ce este asta?
Wh-What's this?
Un mulțumesc pentru tot ce ai făcut până acum.
A thank you for everything until now.
Un mulțumesc?
A thank you?
Este ceva în neregulă?
Is something wrong?
Nu.
No.
Nimic.
Nothing.
SHAGGAI
Alo, eu sunt.
Hello, it's me.
Poți să aduni gașca?
Can you get the gang together?
Da, cât mai repede posibil.
Yeah, as soon as possible.
Este ceva...
There's something...
Voiam să te întreb de ceva vreme, dar...
I've wanted to ask for a while, but...
Ce anume?
What is it?
Prima dată când ne-am întâlnit la cafenea...
The first time we met at the cafe...
Don't you say good-bye
Atunci...
Back then...
De ce nu ai fugit?
Why didn't you run away?
I want you to be there for me
A-Asta pentru că eram interesată de tine atunci, Ryou.
Th-That was because I was interested in you back then, Ryou.
Ryou?
Single rainy day
Shy baby face
I'm remembering tonight...
Once again, the two of us back then
At night, I want to embrace you
I want our heartbeats to overlap
Treabă excelentă!
Great job!
Let me hear today's hit song, that love song
Nohara
Group
Nohara Group
Milady, aveți un apel telefonic.
Milady, you have a telephone call.
Hei, Maki, e grav!
Hey, Maki, this is bad!
Sora ta și ceilalți sunt cu monstrul.
Your sister and the others are with the monster.
Nu știu ce s-ar putea
întâmpla. Sunt la...
I don't know what might
happen. They're at...
Clădirea aceasta este
abandonată de doi ani.
This building has been
abandoned for two years.
Așa că o folosim din când în când.
So we use it from time to time.
Este bună pentru lucruri de genul acesta.
It's good for things like this.
Ei bine...
Now then...
Ryou! Ryou!
Noaptea este lungă.
Să ne distrăm.
The night is long.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
Încet și pe îndelete!
Nice and slowly!
Rumi!
Din ce spun prietenii mei,
te transformi într-un adevărat monstru.
From what my friends say,
you turn into a real monster.
Ei bine...
Now then...
Să vedem monstrul!
Let's see the monster!
Știu să mă apăr!
I-I know how to defend myself!
Vino și ia-o!
Come and get it!
Justice
Milady, nu puteți folosi
așa ceva!
Milady, you cannot take
something like that!
Justice
Așteptați! Milady!
Wait! Milady!
Acum, cine urmează?!
Now, who's next?!
Ești puternică.
You're strong.
Îmi plac fetele puternice.
I like strong girls.
Ryou!
Ryou...
Asta e tare!
This is cool!
Hai să terminăm, nenorocitule!
Let's do it, you bastard!
Își va reveni curând.
Își va reveni... Își va reveni curând.
He'll return to normal soon.
He'll return... He'll return soon.
Fă ceva!
E-Este iubitul tău, nu?!
Do something!
H-He's your boyfriend, right?!
Hei, Rumi!
Hey, Rumi!
Perversule! Lașule!
You pervert! You weakling!
Tu... Tu...
You... You...
Sugiura Ryou...
Idiotule!
You idiot!
Îmi amintesc!
I remember!
Mi-am pierdut memoria după
ce am absorbit această formă de viață.
I lost my memory after
I absorbed this life form.
C-Ce? Ce se întâmplă?
Wh-What? What's going on?
Ryou!
E-Eu sunt...
I-I am...
Eu sunt un colecționar!
I am a collector!
Toate formele de viață, din toate lumile...
All life forms, from all the worlds...
Oprește-te!
Stop!
Rumi!
R-Ryou!
De ce? De ce o parte din colecția mea...
Why? Why is a part of my collection...
De ce?!
Why?!
Taci! Taci!
Shut up! Shut up!
Te rog...
Please...
Pleacă.
Leave.
Pleacă!
Leave!
Sunt Sugiura din Mitaka.
I'm Sugiura from Mitaka.
Ăă...
Um...
Când mă masturbez,
văd lumini și aud păsări,
When I masturbate,
I see lights and hear birds,
iar când mă trezesc,
camera mea este complet devastată.
and when I wake up,
my room is all trashed.
Salut, aici este Madonna de Comunicare
prin Telefon.
Hi, this is Telephone
Communication Madonna.
Salut, aici este Madonna de
Comunicare prin Telefon.
Hi, this is Telephone
Communication Madonna.
Sunt Yumi, cu cine vorbesc?
This is Yumi, and you are?
Ah, chiar?
Oh, really?
Bună, aici este Telecom Madonna.
Hello, this is Telecom Madonna.
Este suficient de bine?
Is that good enough?
Așa, ce dorești?
So what do you want?
C-Ce porți acum?
Wh-What are you wearing right now?
Ce culoare are lenjeria ta?
What color is your underwear?
Am auzit că sora mea lucrează aici, așa că...
I heard my sister was working here, so...
Da, este doar a doua ei zi, dar am auzit că se descurcă foarte bine.
Yeah, it's only her second day, but I hear she's picking it up.
Toată lumea este foarte impresionată.
Everyone's really impressed.
Mi-e frică!
I'm scared!
YUI INC
Gata!
I'm done!
Am reușit!
Yay!
Perversule.
Per-ver-t.
TONIGHT
Orphan Fansubs presents
I poured blue moonlight in the glass
and put it to my lips
I'll cheer up the pain in your aching heart
No one is waiting for a stimulus
Let's invite passion to the sky
Sweet music, that's it
Two people in motion in the sky
Please call me tonight, don't forget
Please call me tonight, once again
I'm gazing at the changing signal
Shifting tension in the wave
The night seems devious and anxious
Tearful motion in the wave
Please call me tonight, please
Please call me tonight, once again